<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on AVX&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on AVX&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2022 AdvancedVectorExtensions</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing EasyAntiCheat&#39;s CR3 Protection</title>
      <link>/2022/12/11/easyanticheat-cr3-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/12/11/easyanticheat-cr3-protection/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As the desire for competitive gaming intensifies, so does the need to ensure that all players are on a level playing field. Enter EasyAntiCheat - the formidable wall between cheaters and legitimately minded players. This ingeniously crafted system utilizes sophisticated algorithms and cutting-edge software to detect, prevent and protect players from a variety of nefarious activities. Through its ability to stay one step ahead of modern cheating tactics, EasyAntiCheat has become the go-to solution for many gaming communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defeating BattlEye&#39;s Dll Protection</title>
      <link>/2022/11/29/battleye-dll-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/11/29/battleye-dll-protection/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The anti-cheat software BattlEye, considered the gold standard, has a catastrophic weakness that makes it easy for an attacker to insert code into the game&amp;rsquo;s address space.
Dll injection is a well-known idea, but because of the numerous anti-cheat techniques used, attackers have resorted to manually mapping their modules into the game&amp;rsquo;s address space in order to get beyond the checks employed.
Load Image Callback Several separate callbacks will initially be registered by the BattlEye driver when it is loaded into the kernel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defeating Vanguard&#39;s Import Protection</title>
      <link>/2022/11/24/vanguard-import-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/11/24/vanguard-import-protection/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Valorant, being a highly competitive game, demands that there be no cheats and calls for the highest level of protection.
In order to prevent an attacker from studying the game and anticheat&amp;rsquo;s internal behaviour, Vanguard, the line between heroes and cheats, employs a variety of techniques, such as import protection.
Import protection is crucial because it prevents malicious actors from drawing firm conclusions about the actions of the code, even inside virtualized methods.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
